Guide to the Julio Elizalde Papers [Guía a los escritos de Julio Elizalde], 1973-2007 LATINAMER.2013.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Writings, 1972-2007; I.
  - Writings, March-July 1983 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Anexo #2: Al Mensaje #2 Dirigido al Gral John W. Vessey, Jefe del Estado Mayor Conjunto [Annex #2: Message #2 Addressed to General John W. Vessey, Chairman of the Join Chiefs of Staff], 19 de mayo, 1983 [May 19, 1983]; 18.; 2 pages
    - Cuarto Mensaje al Gral Vessey, Jefe del Estado Mayor Conjunto [Fourth Message to General Vessey, Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff], 30 de mayo, 1983 [May 30, 1983]; 19.; 2 pages
    - Un estudio político: Estados Unidos frente al drama mundial: Una evaluación global de la situación [A Political Study: The United States in Front of the World Drama: A Global Evaluation of the Situation], 7 de junio, 1983 [June 7, 1983]; 20.; 25 pages
    - Correspondencia a Dominguez [Correspondence to Dominguez], 7 de junio, 1983 [June 7, 1983]; 21.; 1 page
    - Abrazos a Dominguez [Hugs to Dominguez], 19 de julio - 29 de julio, 1983 [July 19 - July 29, 1983]; 22.; 3 pages
  - Writings, July-December 1983 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Nota muy importante [Very Important Note], 23 de julio, 1983 [July 23, 1983]; 1.; 3 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 15 de agosto, 1983 [August 15, 1983]; 2.; 3 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 21 de agosto, 1983 [August 21, 1983]; 3.; 4 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 29 de agosto, 1983 [August 29, 1983]; 4.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 2 de septiembre, 1983 [September 2, 1983]; 5.; 3 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 4 de septiembre, 1983 [September 4, 1983]; 6.; 4 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 4 de septiembre, 1983 [September 4, 1983]; 7.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 6 de septiembre, 1983 [September 6, 1983]; 8.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 12 de septiembre, 1983 [September 12, 1983]; 9.; 1 page
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 15 de septiembre, 1983 [September 15, 1983]; 10.; 3 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 13 de octubre, 1983 [October 13, 1983]; 11.; 2 pages
    - Memorándum: Tiene carácter de urgencia que la alianza militar con la República Popular China quede establecida [Memorandum: It Is A Matter of Urgency That the Military Alliance with the People's Republic of China Remains Established], 4 de noviembre, 1983 [November 4, 1983]; 12.; 4 pages
    - Memorándum: Los pronunciamientos del Primer Ministro de Israel, Yitzhak Shamir [Memorandum: The Declarations of the Prime Minister of Israel, Yitzhak Shamir], 7 de noviembre, 1983 [November 7, 1983]; 13.; 3 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 26 de noviembre, 1983 [November 26, 1983]; 14.; 1 page
    - Nota especial: La República Popular China: Eje de la estabilidad mundial [Special Note: The People's Republic of China: The Axis of World Stability], 27 de noviembre, 1983 [November 27, 1983]; 15.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 30 de noviembre, 1983 [November 30, 1983]; 16.; 1 page
    - Nota muy breve [Very Brief Note], 1 de diciembre, 1983 [December 1, 1983]; 17.; 1 page
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 5 de diciembre, 1983 [December 5, 1983]; 18.; 1 page
    - Nota muy breve: El estado #51 [Very Brief Note: The 51st State], 6 de diciembre, 1983 [December 6, 1983]; 19.; 1 page
    - Nota breve: La tragedia del 23 de octubre [Brief Note: The Tragedy of October 23rd], 24 de diciembre, 1983 [December 24, 1983]; 20.; 1 page
    - Nota especial: Para ser añadida a la intensa correspondencia elevada en las últimas horas [Special Note: To Be Added to the Intense Correspondenced Raised in the Last Hours], 26 de diciembre, 1983 [December 26, 1983]; 21.; 4 pages
    - Un estudio político: La lucha, DECISIVA, Washington-Moscú.- El sofisma, base operacional de los medios de difusión.- Análisis de ejemplos concretos en los que los medios de difusiones han aplicado, recientemente, la sofística.- La entrevista Shultz-Gromyko.- Es suicida el diferir el establecimiento formal de una alianza militar Estados Unidos-República Popular China [A Political Study: The DECISIVE Washington-Moscow Struggle.- Sophism, Operational Base of the Media.- Analysis of Concrete Examples in Which the Media Has Recently Applied Sophistry.- Shultz-Gromyko Interview.- It is Suicide to Differ the Formal Establishment of a Military Alliance between the Untied States and the People's Republic of China], 31 de diciembre, 1983 [December 31, 1983]; 22.; 6 pages
  - Writings, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 2 de enero, 1984 [January 2, 1984]; 1.; 1 page
    - Un estudio político: El discurso de Reagan, Segunda parte [A Political study: Reagan's Speech, Second Part], 18 de enero, 1984 [January 18, 1984]; 2.; 4 pages
    - Nota [Note], 31 de enero, 1984 [January 31, 1984]; 3.; 1 page
    - Reflexiones desde la cima del drama político mundial: La muerte de Andropov, un análisis global de la lucha a muerte Washington-Moscou, Introducción, Para: Dirección Política [Reflections from the Heights of World Political Conflict: The Death of Andropov, A global analysis of the fight to death between Washington and Moscow, Introduction, To: Political Direction], 11 de febrero, 1984 [February 11, 1984]; 4.; 8 pages
    - Reflexiones desde la cima del drama político mundial: La muerte de Andropov, un análisis global de la lucha a muerte Washington-Moscou, Segunda Parte, Para: Dirección Política de los Orgnaismos de Seguridad [Reflections from the Heights of World Political Conflict: The Death of Andropov, A global analysis of the fight to death between Washington and Moscow, Part Two, To: Political Direction of the Security Agencies], 12 de febrero, 1984 [February 12, 1984]; 5.; 8 pages
    - Reflexiones desde la cima del drama político mundial: La muerte de Andropov, un análisis global de la lucha a muerte Washington-Moscou, Conclusión, Para: Dirección Política de los Organismos de Seguridad [Reflections from the Heights of World Political Conflict: The Death of Andropov, A global analysis of the fight to death between Washington and Moscow, Conclusion, To: Political Direction of the Security Agencies], 13 de febrero, 1984 [February 13, 1984]; 6.; 8 pages
    - Un mensaje a los a servicios de Inteligencia del Japón [A Message to the Intelligence Services of Japan], 19 de febrero, 1984 [February 19, 1984]; 7.; 3 pages
    - Breves observaciones, Para: Dirección Política de los Organismos de Seguridad [Brief Observations, To: Political Direction of the Security Agencies], 20 de febrero, 1984 [February 20, 1984]; 8.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 4 de marzo, 1984 [March 4, 1984]; 9.; 2 pages
    - Estudios desde la cima: Una evaluación política mundial, I. Las evidencias afirman que el apaciguamiento no contiene al agresor II. Un segundo rostro del apaciguamiento al enemigo III. Distintos episodios de la capitulación, Para: Dirección Política [Studies from the Heights: A Global Political Evaluation, I. The evidence affirms that appeasement does not subdue the aggressor. II. A second face of the appeasement of the enemy III. Distinct episodes of capitulation, To: Political Direction], 13 de marzo, 1984 [March 13, 1984]; 10.; 12 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 19 de marzo, 1984 [March 19, 1984]; 11.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 5 de abril, 1984 [April 5, 1984]; 12.; 3 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 6 de abril, 1984 [April 6, 1984]; 13.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 11 de abril, 1984 [April 11, 1984]; 14.; 3 pages
    - Nota breve (Para ser añadida a la carta política elevada en la mañana de hoy) [Brief Note (To be added to the political letter raised today in the morning)], 13 de abril, 1984 [April 13, 1984]; 15.; 2 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 15 de abril, 1984 [April 15, 1984]; 16.; 5 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 17 de abril, 1984 [April 17, 1984]; 17.; 5 pages
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 22 de abril, 1984 [April 22, 1984]; 18.; 7 pages
    - Nota (para ser añadida al Mensaje Especial enviado hace una hora, quizá menos) [Note (to be added to the Special Message sent an hour ago, perhaps earlier)], 26 de mayo, 1984 [May 26, 1984]; 19.; 1 page
    - Nota Breve [Brief Note], 16 de junio, 1984 [June 16, 1984]; 20.; 1 page
    - Cuestiones internas [Internal Questions], 15 de julio, 1984 [July 15, 1984]; 21.; 1 page
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 18 de julio, 1984 [July 18, 1984]; 22.; 1 page
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 23 de julio, 1984 [July 23, 1984]; 23.; 2 pages
    - Análisis: El discurso de Castro [Analysis: Castro's Speech], 27 de julio, 1984 [July 27, 1984]; 24.; 3 pages
    - Análisis: Aspectos viscerales de la traición al pueblo americano [Analysis: Visceral Aspects of the Betrayal of the American People], 30 de julio, 1984 [July 30, 1984]; 25.; 5 pages
    - Cuestiones internas [Internal Questions], 30 de julio, 1984 [July 30, 1984]; 26.; 1 page
    - Correspondencia a Mr. Wilson [Correspondence to Mr. Wilson], 12 de agosto, 1984 [August 12, 1984]; 27.; 2 pages
    - Análisis: Sin sólidos principios morales, es imposible coronar con éxito una gran empresa [Analysis: Without Solid Moral Principles, It is Impossible to Successfully Achieve a Great Business], 25 de agosto, 1984 [August 25, 1984]; 28.; 4 pages
    - Mensaje a la Comisión [Message to the Commission], 26 de septiembre, 1984 [September 26, 1984]; 29.; 1 page
    - Análisis: El terrorismo [Analysis: Terrorism], 1 de octubre, 1984 [October 1, 1984]; 30.; 2 pages
    - Reflexiones, Para: Departamento Político del Buró Federal de Investigaciones [Reflections, To: Political Department of the Federal Bureau of Investigations], 14 de noviembre, 1984 [November 14, 1984]; 31.; 5 pages
    - Breves reflexiones, Para: Departamento Político del Buró Federal de Investigaciones [Brief Reflections, To: Political Department of the Federal Bureau of Investigations], 17 de noviembre, 1984 [November 17, 1984]; 32.; 3 pages
    - Observaciones, Para: Departamento Político [Observations, To: Political Department], 19 de noviembre, 1984 [November 19, 1984]; 33.; 2 pages
    - Observaciones, Para: Defense Intelligence Agency [Observations, To: Defense Intelligence Agency], 25 de noviembre, 1984 [November 25, 1984]; 34.; 3 pages
    - Observaciones, Para: Defense Intelligence Agency [Observations, To: Defense Intelligence Agency], 26 de noviembre, 1984 [November 26, 1984]; 35.; 4 pages
    - Al leadership [To the Leadership], 14 de diciembre, 1984 [December 14, 1981]; 36.; 1 page
    - Reflexiones, Para: Buró Federal de Investigaciones, Defense Intelligence Agency [Reflections, To: Federal Bureau of Investigations, Defense Intelligence Agency], 23 de diciembre, 1984 [December 23, 1984]; 37.; 4 pages
    - Estudios políticos desde la cima: Washington, Catastróficas consecuencias de una específica política exterior, Para: Departamento Político del Buró Federal de Investigaciones, Defense Intelligence Agency [Political Studies from the Heights: Washington, Catastrophic Consequences of a Specific Foreign Policy, To: Political Department of the Federal Bureau of Investigations, Defense Intelligence Agency], 27 de diciembre, 1984 [December 27, 1984]; 38.; 4 pages
  - Writings, January-October 1985 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Memorándum: Moscú no cree en lágrimas [Memorandum: Moscow does not believe in tears], 3 de enero, 1985 [January 3, 1985]; 1.; 2 pages
    - Estudios políticos desde la cima: La ofensiva soviética y la desintegración del mundo libre, Para: F.B.I. [Political Studies from the Heights: The Offensive Soviet and the Political Collapse of the Free World, To: F.B.I.], 4 de enero, 1985 [January 4, 1985]; 2.; 5 pages
    - Estudios políticos desde la cima: La ofensiva soviética y la desintegración política de Occidente, Para: F.B.I. [Political Studies from the Heights: The Offensive Soviet and the Political Collapse of the West, To: F.B.I.], 6 de enero, 1985 [January 6, 1985]; 3.; 7 pages
    - Análisis: Capitulación en Ginebra, Para: F.B.I. [Analysis: Capitulation in Geneva, To: F.B.I.], 8 de enero, 1985 [January 8, 1985]; 4.; 3 pages
    - Al leadership, Para: F.B.I. [To the Leadership, To: F.B.I.], 16 de enero - 13 de febrero, 1985 [January 16 - February 13, 1985]; 5.; 6 pages
    - Estudios políticos desde la cima: ¿Fue violada la correspondencia secreta? ¿Qué explicación tiene que el trabajo de análisis avanzara en un sentido, y la Casa Blanca y el Departamento de Estado en otro?, Para: F.B.I. [Political Studies from the Heights: Was the secret correspondence violated? What explanation is there that the work of analysis advances in one direction, and the White House and the Department of State in another?, To: F.B.I.], 23 de enero, 1985 [January 23, 1985]; 6.; 5 pages
    - Al Leadership [To the Leadership], 23 de enero, 1985 [January 23, 1985]; 7.; 1 page
    - Al Leadership [To the Leadership], 29 de enero, 1985 [January 29, 1985]; 8.; 1 page
    - Un mensaje sumamente importante, Para: F.B.I. [A Highly Important Message, To: F.B.I.], 12 de marzo, 1985 [March 12, 1985]; 9.; 3 pages
    - A la División Política [To the Political Division], 15 de marzo, 1985 [March 15, 1985]; 10.; 1 page
    - Otro mensaje a la División Política [Another Message to the Political Division], 19 de marzo, 1985 [March 19, 1985]; 11.; 3 pages
    - Nota breve: El incidente República Popular China-Corea del Sur [Brief Note: The People's Republic of China-South Korean Incident], 24 de marzo, 1985 [March 24, 1985]; 12.; 1 page
    - Nota muy importante: El asesinato del soldado americano en Alemania del East, Para: F.B.I. [Very Important Note: The Assassination of the American Soldier in East Germany, To: F.B.I.], 25 de marzo, 1985 [March 25, 1985]; 13.; 2 pages
    - A la División Política [To the Political Division], 11 de abril, 1985 [April 11, 1985]; 14.; 1 page
    - Palabras importantes, Para: División Política, División Criminal [Important Words, To: Political Division, Criminal Division], 15 de abril, 1985 [April 15, 1985]; 15.; 1 page
    - A la División Política y División Criminal [To the Political Division and Criminal Division], 16 de abril, 1985 [April 16, 1985]; 16.; 1 page
    - Grito de Alarma, Para: División Política, División Criminal [Cry of Alarm, To: Political Division, Criminal Division], 19 de abril, 1985 [April 19, 1985]; 17.; 3 pages
    - Observaciones extremadamente importantes, Para: División Política, División Criminal [Extremely Important Observations, To: Political Division, Criminal Division], 19 de abril, 1985 [April 19, 1985]; 18.; 4 pages
    - Un breve mensaje [A Brief Message], 30 de abril, 1985 [April 30, 1985]; 19.; 1 page
    - Ampliación analítica (Para ser añadida al Mensaje Urgente al Estado Mayor del Army, elevado en la mañana de hoy, martes 7 de mayo de 1985) [Analytical Extension (To be added to the Urgent Message to the Head of the Army, sent in the morning of today, Tuesday, May 7, 1985)], 4 de mayo, 1985 [May 4, 1985]; 20.; 2 pages
    - Notas (Para ser añadidas a las Observaciones Elevadas en la mañana de hoy, jueves 9 de mayo, 1985) [Notes (To be added to the Raised Observations in the morning of today, Thursday, May 9, 1985)], 7 de mayo, 1985 [May 7, 1985]; 21.; 3 pages
    - Una breve aclaración [A brief clarification], 15 de mayo, 1985 [May 15, 1985]; 22.; 1 page
    - Aclaración super importante, Para: División Política, División Criminal [Super Important Clarification, To: Political Division, Criminal Division], 16 de mayo, 1985 [May 16, 1985]; 23.; 2 pages
    - Dos reflexiones, exclusivamente dos pero extremadamente importantes, Para: División Política [Two reflections, exclusively two but extremely important, To: Political Division], 20 de mayo, 1985 [May 20, 1985]; 24.; 3 pages
    - Análisis extremadamente importante, Para: División Política, División Criminal [Extremely important analysis, To: Political Division, Criminal Division], 28 de mayo, 1985 [May 28, 1985]; 25.; 2 pages
    - Observaciones [Observations], 7 de junio, 1985 [June 7, 1985]; 26.; 2 pages
    - Una denuncia extremadamente grave, Para: División Política, Fuerzas Armadas Americanas [An extremely serious complaint, To: Political Division, American Armed Forces], 12 de julio, 1985 [July 12, 1985]; 27.; 3 pages
    - Observaciones extremadamente importantes [Extremely Important Observations], 13 de junio, 1985 [June 13, 1985]; 28.; 2 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: Unas breves reflexiones, Para: División Política, División Criminal, Estado Mayor del Army [At the Heights of World Conflict: Some Brief Reflections, To: Political Division, Criminal Division, Head of Army], 11 de julio, 1985 [July 11, 1985]; 29.; 4 pages
    - Una reflexión filosófico-política extremadamente importante (Para ser añadida al Mensaje Elevado en la mañana de hoy) [An extremely important philosophical-political reflection (To be added to the Raised Message in the morning of today)], 17 de julio, 1985 [July 17, 1985]; 30.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje a la División Política [A Message to the Political Division], 18 de julio, 1985 [July 18, 1985]; 31.; 2 pages
    - Un mensaje, relacionado con la lucha, Para: División Política, Estado Mayor del Army [A Message, Related with the Fight, To: Political Division, Head of Army], 24 de julio, 1985 [July 24, 1985]; 32.; 2 pages
    - *Observaciones, Para: Departamento Político del Army [Observations, To: Political Department of the Army], 30 de julio, 1985 [July 30, 1985]; 33.; 2 pages
    - Observaciones, Para: Departamento Político, División Político [Observations, To: Political Department, Political Division], 6 de agosto, 1985 [August 6, 1985]; 34.; 1 page
    - Un breve mensaje, Para: Departamento Político, División Política [A Brief Message, To: Political Department, Political Division], 6 de agosto, 1985 [August 6, 1985]; 35.; 1 page
    - Reflexiones, Para: Departamento Político, División Político [Reflections, To: Political Department, Political Division], 7 de agosto 1985 [August 7, 1985]; 36.; 2 pages
    - Observaciones muy importantes, Para: División Política [Very Important Observations, To: Political Division], 27 de agosto, 1985 [August 27, 1985]; 37.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje crucialmente importante, Para: División Política [A Crucially Important Message, To: Political Division], 31 de agosto, 1985 [August 31, 1985]; 38.; 2 pages
    - Reflexiones, Para: La Comisión [Reflections, To: The Commission], 17 de septiembre, 1985 [September 17, 1985]; 39.; 2 pages
    - A la Comisión [To the Commission], 17 de septiembre, 1985 [September 17, 1985]; 40.; 1 page
    - Análisis: Alea jacta est, Para: La Comisión [Analysis: Alea jacta est, To: The Commission], 29 de septiembre, 1985 [September 29, 1985]; 41.; 4 pages
    - Observaciones, Para: La Comisión [Observations, To: The Commission], 19 de octubre, 1985 [October 19, 1985]; 42.; 3 pages
    - Un mensaje extremadamente importante, Para: La Comisión [An Extremely Important Message, To: The Commission], 22 de octubre, 1985 [October 22, 1985]; 43.; 4 pages
    - Un estudio político: Un caballo de Troya, Para: La Comisión [A Political Study: A Trojan Horse, To: The Comission], 24 de octubre, 1985 [October 24, 1985]; 44.; 4 pages
    - Sin título [Untitled], 27 de octubre, 1985 [October 27, 1985]; 45.; 3 pages
    - Análisis: Peligrosísimo agente del "Caballo de Troya," George P. Shultz debe ser inmediatamente destituido [Analysis: Very Dangerous Agent of "Trojan Horse," George P. Shultz Should be Immediately Dismissed], 30 de octubre, 1985 [October 30, 1985]; 46.; 5 pages
    - Análisis: Si los "Organismos de Seguridad" no lo evitan, Ronald Reagan destruirá al Occidente. Si las fuerzas que, dentro de los Estados Unidos, podrían ayudarlo a enfrentarse al drama mundial se niegan a hacerlo, ¿por qué no abandona la Casa Blanca antes de que la catástrofe sea irreversible? [Analysis: If the "Security Agencies" do not prevent it, Ronald Reagan will destroy the West. If the forces that, within the United States, would be able to help him confront world conflicts refuse to do it, why doesn't the White House quit before the catastrophe becomes irreversible?], 31 de octubre, 1985 [October 31, 1985]; 47.; 6 pages
  - Writings, November-December 1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - A la Comisión [To the Commission], 1 de noviembre, 1985 [November 1, 1985]; 1.; 1 page
    - Un breve análisis teórico-político: El desconocimiento de la historia y el divorcio de la realidad, mortalmente amenazan al pueblo americano [A Brief Theoretical-Political Analysis: The Ignorance of History and Divorce from Reality Mortally Threatens the American People], 2 de noviembre, 1985 [November 2, 1985]; 2.; 2 pages
    - A la Comisión con amor [To the Commission with Love], 2 de noviembre, 1985 [November 2, 1985]; 3.; 1 page
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: Si el Army no exige la destitución de Ronald Reagan, la Casa Blanca y el Departamento de Estado destruirán a Occidente. No puede hablarse de que Reagan ha perdido las perspectivas racionales, porque otra vez va a ser probado que nunca las tuvo. Si después de las leídas estas reflexiones automáticamente la crisis nacional no avanza hacia su desenlace, la responsabilidad de la tragedia global va a recaer sobre el ala militar del pentágono y los "Organismos de Seguridad" [At the Heights of World Conflict: If the Army does not demand the dismissal of Ronald Reagan, the White House and Department of State will destroy the West. It cannot be said that Reagan has lost rational perspectives, because once again it will be proven that he never had them. If after reading these reflections the national crisis does not automatically advances towards its solution, the responsibility of the global tragedy will fall again on military wing of the Pentagon and the "Security Agencies"], 3 de noviembre, 1985 [November 3, 1985]; 4.; 6 pages
    - A la Comisión con amor inmaculado [To the Commission With Immaculate Love], 3 de noviembre, 1985 [November 3, 1985]; 5.; 2 pages
    - Un mensaje a la Comisión [A message to the Commission], 7 de noviembre, 1985 [November 7, 1985]; 6.; 2 pages
    - Un mensaje a la División Política [A Message to the Political Division], 7 de noviembre, 1985 [November 7, 1985]; 7.; 5 pages
    - Mensaje #3 al Ala Militar del Pentágono [Message #3 to the Military Wing of the Pentagon], 13 de noviembre, 1985 [November 13, 1985]; 8.; 4 pages
    - Nota: Al Ala Military del Pentágono [Note: To the Military Wing of the Pentagon], 15 de noviembre, 1985 [November 15, 1985]; 9.; 1 page
    - Nota analítica [Analytical Note], 20 de noviembre, 1985 [November 20, 1985]; 10.; 1 page
    - Reflexiones, Para: Servicios de Inteligencia del Navy [Reflections, To: Intelligence Services of the Navy], 26 de noviembre, 1985 [November 26, 1985]; 11.; 3 pages
    - Desde la cima del drama mundial: La desintegración de los Estados Unidos y las relaciones con el Estado de Israel [At the Heights of World Conflict: The Disintegration of the United States and Relations with the State of Israel], 30 de noviembre, 1985 [November 30, 1985]; 12.; 8 pages